You know, we've got a lot of
only children in our group, huh?
Only child
I've got a little brother.
And I have an older sister.
You have a point, though.
Also only children
But the biggest shock of them all
is that Shu's an older brother.
What?
Wait, you didn't know?
A sister?
A brother?
Or a sister?
Or a brother?
Calm down, he doesn't have that many!
I only found out when I went over
to Shu's house not too long ago.
I'm back!
Thanks for having me over.
Hey.
Try to keep it down.
You got it.
And don't touch me.
Oh, hello.
Your little sister?
Yup, three years younger.
I totally figured his
little sister would be all...
Tee-hee! Welcome home, big bwuther!
They look pretty similar,
but she wasn't all that friendly with him.
Wow. Can't believe Iura's a big brother.
He's a big bwuther...
He's pretty chill outside of school.
Whoa, really?
'Sup, my dudes!
Let's go get ourselves burgerfied
after school, whaddya think?!
You'd better start
acting more responsible!
What?!
Horimiya
Student
Council
Room
It May Seem Like Hate
Psych! Just kidding!
God, Shu, you're such a clown.
Iura- kun is quite the comedian, isn't he?
Hey, Yanagi- kun ,
why do you always talk so formally?
Wait, I do?
Yeah, you've been super polite
to us ever since the day we met.
Sorry, I suppose it's just habit.
But you're real casual with Yuki.
Really?
Yeah, just the other day...
Bye-bye!
Oh, goodbye.
Yanagin, "bye-bye"!
Right...
Yanagin! Bye-bye!
B... Bye-bye.
Ohmigod, you said it! You're so cute!
Remi-Remi, I don't know if I should
be impressed or weirded out.
Thanks for waiting, Hori.
What's going on there?
Ayasaki- san 's messing with Yanagi- kun .
Whoa.
Oh, are you guys heading home? Bye-bye!
Bye. See you, Yanagi- kun .
Goodbye.
Later.
Yeah. Later.
See?
I'm not sure why that is...
I'd sure like to know why.
Okay, Yanagi, why don't you start
calling everyone by their first name?
Huh?!
I'll call you Akane!
It's times like these that I get really
jealous of Iura's peppy personality.
Everyone wants to be
closer friends with Yanagi
You can use my first name, too!
Everyone wants to be
closer friends with Yanagi
I've never called a friend
by their first name before.
I don't think it will come easily to me.
No! Stop using your polite voice!
Huh?
No more formal talk, starting now!
What?!
Owie!
Stop bothering Yanagi.
Oh, no, he's certainly not bothering me...
I... Well, I can assure you,
not even I appreciate the fact...
...that I keep such distance between
myself and others with my words.
But I'd like to become closer friends
with Ishikawa- kun and Miyamura- kun ...
And of course, all the rest of you, too.
What's going on in here?
This is quite the odd bunch.
SQUEEZE
Look, Yanagi, we weren't friends with
this guy here until recently, either!
SQUEEZE
Hey !
But look how close we
are now! Isn't that great?
SQUEEZE
Boy, you couldn't pay me
to do that with the Prez.
They managed to creep out Iura- kun !
That's quite the feat,
Ishikawa- kun , Miyamura- kun !
Sengoku! We're good buds now, right?
What?!
We got to be best buds right away, too!
We are n--
O-Of course we're best buds!
I'm best buds with all
of you, Yanagi- kun , too!
Way to go, Prez!
For real! Let's finish 'im
off with a wrestling move!
Guys are so weird.
I'm gonna go follow Yuki.
H-Hey, no wrestling holds!
Best buds...
Best buds can settle any argument
with rock-paper-scissors!
Don't blatantly lie to him, Ishikawa- kun !
Yeah! The poor prez always loses!
You lose way more than I do!
Really?
Who knows.
I'm not that bad at
rock-paper-scissors, am I?
How do you not know?
You lose every time we decide
who goes to the vending machines.
Fine, then I'll win next time.
Hey, uh...
Would it be all right if I
called you "Toru," Ishikawa- kun ?
Sure!
What about me? What about me , Akane?
One at a time! Please,
let me do this one at a time!
Well, I wanna be next!
Are you gonna start calling him Akane?
It'd be weird if I were the only one.
I mean, I could,
I just need a bit of time.
Huh.
What?
Nothing.
Yanagi- kun might be on my
personal blacklist, I guess.
Wait, why?! Why's he on your blacklist?!
Just kidding.
What?!
Sorry, forget it.
That's not a very funny joke, you know!
Miyamura- kun .
I won't take them away.
Huh? Take what away?
What's he gonna take from you?
Or did he already take it?
Sh-Shut up!
Argh
C'mon, what is it?
You dummy!
You're a big dummy, Akane!
And there he goes.
What the heck was he talking about?
Yanagi looks happy 'bout it, at least.
Look, I told you, you're wrong!
No, I'm telling you...
Oh, Kono- san !
Kono- san !
I'm taller than him by a little, right?
We're the same height, aren't we?
Wait, are you two fighting or something?
Not at all! Akane just said he got taller.
And Miyamura- kun said I didn't!
So you are fighting.
No, because I'm taller than Akane!
Well, I told him neither of us are 170
centimeters tall, and he got all mad!
That was uncalled for, Miyamura- kun .
And you shouldn't have
blown up at him either, Yanagi- kun !
I'm sorry.
Hey! You beat me to apologizing! No fair!
It's completely fair. I'm sorry.
You did it again!
I'm glad the two of them
are such close friends.
Sawada, how do you feel about this one?
Normal.
What about this one?
Wow, you've gotten a lot
better with guys lately, huh.
You know, we're your friends,
not inanimate objects.
That's right.
Sorry, I just wanted to see how
comfortable Sawada's getting with guys.
I can handle up to Sengoku.
"Hori- senpai -& Girls -& Miyamura -& Boys
[Ishikawa -& Sengoku -&
Shindo -& Iura (Yanagi?)]"
Wait, where do I rank, then?!
Ishikawa: Nice. Talks to me.
Sengoku: Easy to talk to.
Shindou: When I go to Miyamura's house, I get
scared
sometimes.
Iura: Loud. Like, really loud. And annoying.
Yanagi → I haven't talked so much.
Sweet!
I've got some snacks here, Sawada- san .
You like chocolate, Sawada- san ?
You can have all of these!
Look, she's eatin' them
right outta my hand!
Just you wait.
I'll shake up that tier list.
What the heck...
Iura- kun , not a peep! Stay quiet!
Huh? What? Sorry, I can't hear you!
Hey, Sawada- san !
Nope!
Huh?! C'mon, now,
Sawada- san , it's me, Iura!
Nope!
Iura- kun , you've got some learning to do.
What am I learning?!
Sawada, Iura- kun isn't trying
to scare you. He's a good guy.
Miyamura!
I mean, I don't care if he's a good guy.
That's not the problem.
Sorry, Iura- kun . No luck.
I can't stand people
who are loud and annoying.
My throat's all scratchy.
You coming down with a cold, Iura?
You keep coughing.
I don't feel sick. I just can't talk.
Well, you're acting
like the same old Iura...
But I do feel... kinda fatigued.
You're totally sick! Go home!
C'mon, you've totally got a fever, too!
Why're you grabbing me like this?!
Be gentle with me!
My throat's dead!
If it hurts that bad,
then go the hell home!
Don't get anyone else sick!
Science Lab
It's so heavy.
Going the same way so might as well help out,
but can't say anything because his throat hurts
Terrified because someone just
grabbed the box out of her hands
Going the same way so might as well help out,
but can't say anything because his throat hurts
Terrified because someone just
grabbed the box out of her hands
Going the same way so might as well help out,
but can't say anything because his throat hurts
Terrified because someone just
grabbed the box out of her hands
Going the same way so might as well help out,
but can't say anything because his throat hurts
Terrified because someone just
grabbed the box out of her hands
Going the same way so might as well help out,
but can't say anything because his throat hurts
Terrified because someone just
grabbed the box out of her hands
Going the same way so might as well help out,
but can't say anything because his throat hurts
Terrified because someone just
grabbed the box out of her hands
Going the same way so might as well help out,
but can't say anything because his throat hurts
Terrified because someone just
grabbed the box out of her hands
Going the same way so might as well help out,
but can't say anything because his throat hurts
Terrified because someone just
grabbed the box out of her hands
Going the same way so might as well help out,
but can't say anything because his throat hurts
Terrified because someone just
grabbed the box out of her hands
Going the same way so might as well help out,
but can't say anything because his throat hurts
Terrified because someone just
grabbed the box out of her hands
Hey!
Science Lab
H-Hey, uh...
Don't get anyone else sick!
Hey...
Wait, what?
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
Nope!
He's
scary!
Nope!
He's
scary!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
You're so
loud, Iura!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
You're so
loud, Iura!
Nope!
He's
scary!
Man, I went home, gargled mouthwash
and passed out, and I'm feelin' great!
Grats.
At least say the whole word!
Wait, why are you congratulating me
for beating a cold, anyway?
Your little sister's studying for high
school exams. Don't get her sick.
Sawada- san ?
H-Hey...
Do you need Iura- kun ?
Wait, you think he's mad at you?
Yeah.
Does he even get mad?
Huh?
I've never seen him angry, ever.
AND I MANAGED
TO PISS HIM OFF!
H-Hold on, is he really mad at you?
AND I MANAGED
TO PISS HIM OFF!
I can hear him laughing,
so I think you're okay.
Do you want him to like you?
Whoa, it's Kono- san and Sawada- san !
Oh, Miyamura's not here, but Hori- san is!
What're you and Kono- san talking about?
Wait, if it's private,
you don't have to say!
Did everything work out yesterday?
Sheesh, the science room is so far away
from the second-year classrooms.
I was worried you'd end up late to class!
Y-Y-You're so annoying!
And she hates me again.
Iura- kun , your timing is annoying.
M-My timing ?!
Ah, hmm... You want to try for East High?
Yes, sir.
East High, huh. And you're dead set on it?
Huh?
I mean, look. You might
want to aim a rank lower.
Your grades are pretty average.
I don't think your grades in any
subject would be high enough...
But that's not to say that's bad, no.
East High, though... You may want
to think that over once more.
Give it some thought,
then come back to me...
Yo, Moto-Moto. You know where Grampa is?
No.
Mmkay.
Whatever.
I'm not gonna have dinner tonight.
Why not?
I told my teacher where I wanted to go
for high school, and he laughed at me.
Why does him laughing at you
mean you're not gonna eat dinner?
Th-That's not what I meant.
You're going to eat dinner.
You are, okay?
O-Okay, fine.
Where do you wanna go, Moto?
You're gonna laugh, too.
No, I won't. I wanna know
where you wanna go.
East High.
Wait, I thought it was gonna be some
funny name! That's not funny at all!
My teacher didn't laugh
at the name, dummy! He...
H-He laughed at my grades.
What, are they laughably bad?
You're always throwing your notes
and textbooks at me, so I took a peek.
The pages of your textbooks are
worn down from how much you study.
You highlight and write
notes all over them, too.
You're trying really hard.
Which teacher laughed at you? Bring 'im over.
I'll punch his lights out.
I'll do it so you don't have to.
Why?
How? Why?
I try, but my grades keep slipping.
My teacher said it's hopeless.
He said I should "rethink things."
My friends, they... Their grades are
good enough to get in, but mine...
I'm...
What should I do, big bro?
I don't know what to do!
I try, and I try, and I try,
but I can't make it happen.
The East High uniforms suck.
If you don't get in, you'll have
to try a lower-ranked school,
but you could totally get into Katagiri.
Our uniforms are real cute.
You'd look good in 'em.
Just do the best you can.
Mmkay.
And eat your fill of dinner.
Hey, Hori- san , I've got a favor to ask.
Oh! Motoko- chan ?
Iu... er, your brother sent you over, yeah?
Yes.
Come on in!
Thank you for having me.
Head upstairs, the door
right at the top is my room.
Go on in and sit wherever.
I'll go get us some drinks.
Oh, sure.
Hello.
H-Hello.
Hello!
Hello.
Guess she's got two brothers...
You want me to tutor your
little sister? Me? Really?
Kind of. I just want you to see
if she could test into East High.
I mean, if that's all, then sure.
And if there's no way she'll get in,
I want you to tell her straight out.
Wait, really?!
No, I'm kidding.
Just help her out a little,
at least till the exam.
You got it.
He looked like a big brother there.
Sorry for the wait.
You good with hot chocolate?
Yes, thank you.
You look a lot like your brother.
Has anyone ever told you that?
I suppose because both me and
my brother are the quiet, brooding type.
H-He is?
The quiet, brooding type?
I, uh, brought my textbooks,
and my notes and stuff, too.
Oh, don't bother.
I know it's tough trying to study in
a stranger's house right off the bat.
Let's just talk. You get the day off today!
A-Are you sure?
Once you've relaxed a little,
we can get to studying.
If you want more people to talk to,
I can call in our resident high-school
and elementary-school boys.
Hey, bro, who was that girl?
Our friend's little sister, Motoko- chan .
She's here to study.
Huh.
Today I've got banana cupcakes!
Banana!
Let's show her we're rooting for her.
Yeah!
No way! Middle schoolers
have cell phones, now?!
Yeah, everyone has one now.
Damn.
Oh, but I don't have contact
info for much of my class.
I basically only text my brother.
So you two are close.
Not at all!
We barely talk, and when I come home late,
he just sends me an angry text. That's it!
We could be in the same house
and he'll text me instead of talking!
So you are close.
You don't think he hates me?
Lucky Charm
Yo, Shu, what're you so worried about?
Which one will make her
pass the test for sure?
Pick it yourself, moron!
I'll just go with the biggest one, then.
Um, they're all the same size...
Then I'll take the most expensive one.
"Guaranteed Exam Success"
That for your sister?
If she wants it, I guess.
You bought it for her, right?
I'm sure it'll be fine.
Hey, it's snowing.
I hope...
...she doesn't...
...he doesn't...
...hate me.
Hitherto, and Forevermore